https://www.stirlingultracold.com/privacy-policy#cookies

Privacy Policy of Stirling Ultracold, Division of Global Cooling, Inc. | Stirling Ultracold
News
Privacy Policy of Stirling Ultracold, Division of Global Cooling, Inc. Updated September 23, 2019
Stirling Ultracold, division of GLOBAL COOLING, INC. is a leading provider of ultra-low temperature freezers and products for the global research markets. GLOBAL COOLING, INC. recognizes and supports the privacy interests of all persons, and we respect these interests when we collect and process Personal Data.
GLOBAL COOLING, INC. maintains limited data for the purpose of communications such as this. All data will be removed upon request or when there is no activity for a period of six (6) months. This Privacy Notice explains our information practices and the choices you can make about the way your Personal Data is collected and used through our websites.
GLOBAL COOLING, INC. and its affiliates (collectively “GLOBAL COOLING, INC”, “we”, “us”, or “our”) maintain and operate this and other websites including applications (collectively, the “GLOBAL COOLING, INC. Websites” or “Websites”). Because some applications, such as those hosted by a third party on our behalf, may require additional information, or use information in a different way, they may have their own privacy policies and terms and conditions. These applications may also offer you additional choices for managing your Personal Data.
APPLICABILITY OF THIS PRIVACY NOTICE
This Privacy Notice applies to all visitors and users of the GLOBAL COOLING, INC. Websites. Because GLOBAL COOLING, INC. has a global market presence, we may adopt separate privacy policies or additional provisions as necessary to reflect the requirements of applicable local laws in the countries in which we operate.
INFORMATION GLOBAL COOLING, INC. COLLECTS
Personal Data
You may browse many sections of our Websites without providing Personal Data about yourself. However, if you choose to establish a business relationship, apply for employment with us or use the “Contact Us” function, we will collect certain information. GLOBAL COOLING, INC. collects the following categories of information about you:
If we establish a business relationship with you, we collect relevant business information, such as name, contact details including email, account, transaction information and/or any other information provided by you relevant to the business relationship.
If you seek employment with us through the Websites, we collect your name, contact details, the position(s) you’re applying for, your education, employment history and any other information you choose to provide in connection with your application for employment.
If you choose to fill out the “Contact Us” form, we collect contact information that may include your name, email address, phone number, as well as your comments and correspondence in connection with the request.
Collectively, the above categories of information constitute “Personal Data”. Missing or incomplete information may result in GLOBAL COOLING, INC. being unable to perform, or continue to perform, a transaction with you or on your behalf.
Cookies
A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your computer’s hard drive by your web browser when you visit a website. Cookies enable websites to access information about the pages you visit and your actions and preferences (such as login, language, font size, and other display preferences) over a period of time. GLOBAL COOLING, INC. uses cookies to ensure the functioning of the Websites, as well as to provide better service when users return to our Websites. For example, using cookies with the Websites allows you to come back to the Websites or browse without having to resubmit your preferences and other information. In certain instances, Cookies may be considered Personal Data.
You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. However, this may prevent you from taking full advantage of the Websites and some portions of the Websites may not function properly.
USE OF INFORMATION
We use your information to improve your experience and to facilitate the business relationship. Situations where we may use your information, include:
To conduct our business, including fulfilling your requests for products, services, and support, and to create new business.
To communicate about our products and services for marketing purposes.
To carry out the obligations arising from any agreements entered between you and us.
To maintain and improve our Websites, enhance your user experience, tailor the user experience, and to ensure content on the Websites are relevant.
To protect the security of the Websites, our systems, and you.
To comply with our legal obligations.
DATA PROTECTION AND SECURITY MEASURES
Maintaining the security of your information is very important to GLOBAL COOLING, INC. We use reasonable technologies to keep your Personal Data secure, and we implement reasonable security measures, that are designed to protect against the accidental or unlawful destruction loss, misuse, alteration, unauthorized disclosure of, or access to your Personal Data.
PROCESSING OF INFORMATION
GLOBAL COOLING, INC. has a global market presence and is headquartered in the United States with offices, affiliates, employees, representatives, partners, and service providers located around the world. As a result, GLOBAL COOLING, INC. may transfer your information, including your Personal Data to, or process your information in, the United States and/or countries other than the country in which your information was collected or provided.
RECIPIENTS OF INFORMATION
We may share your information, including your Personal Data within the GLOBAL COOLING, INC. group of affiliates to facilitate the business relationship and provide the best customer experience. Furthermore, we may share your information with third parties that assist us with fulfillment of our business objectives, job applicant screening or with the performance and content of our Websites. In the event we sell, assign or transfer all or part of the GLOBAL COOLING, INC. business, we may transfer your personal data to the buyer.
CHOICES REGARDING COMMUNICATIONS
If you no longer wish to receive any marketing communications, remain on a mailing list to which you previously subscribed, or receive any other communication from GLOBAL COOLING, INC., please follow the unsubscribe link in the applicable communication.
LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES
GLOBAL COOLING, INC. Websites may provide links or other directions to the websites of our distributors, sales representatives or other third parties. If you follow a link to a third-party website, please note that we are not responsible for the protection and privacy of any Personal Data you provide while visiting such websites. We encourage you to read third-party websites’ privacy policies and statements.
CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS
California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits users of our Website who are California residents to request a notice identifying the categories of Personal Data we share with third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please submit a written request, specifying that you would like a “California Privacy Notice,” to the following address:
Stirling Ultracold, Division of Global Cooling, Inc.
6000 Poston Road
Athens, OH 45701 USA
Attn: Finance Department
PRIVACY OF CHILDREN
GLOBAL COOLING, INC.’s Websites are general audience Websites. We do not intentionally collect Personal Data from users of the Websites who are under the age of sixteen (16). We request that such individuals do not provide Personal Data.
CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY NOTICE
GLOBAL COOLING, INC. may update this Privacy Notice from time to time as our business, services, or policies change, or as required by law. We encourage you to visit our Websites periodically to stay informed about GLOBAL COOLING INC.’s privacy practices. If we update this Privacy Notice, we will post the updated version of the Privacy Notice on our Websites. Your use of the website following any update to the Notice means that you accept the updated Privacy Notice.
CONTACT US
GLOBAL COOLING, INC. takes reasonable steps to ensure your Personal Data is accurate and up-to-date for the purposes for which it was collected. We encourage you to contact us to update or correct your information if it changes or if you believe that any information we collected about you is inaccurate. Please note that to honor your request, we may require additional information for authentication or other verification purposes.
For any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Notice, our privacy practices, or our processing of your Personal Data, please contact GLOBAL COOLING, INC. at info@stirlingultracold.com or at Stirling Ultracold, Division of Global Cooling, Inc., 6000 Poston Road, Athens, OH 45701 USA.
ADDITIONAL TERMS FOR EU OR EEA VISITORS and USERS
This section of our Privacy Notice (“Additional Terms for EU Visitors and Users”) explains GLOBAL COOLING, INC.’s commitment to comply with the European Union’s General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).
GLOBAL COOLING, INC. is committed to fulfilling our responsibilities in relation to collection, retention, use and other processing of Personal Data that is within the scope of GDPR. Such Personal Data will be processed only for lawful and appropriate purposes. GLOBAL COOLING, INC. has implemented reasonable measures designed to secure Personal Data and to prevent unauthorized or accidental access, erasure, or other misuse of personal data. GLOBAL COOLING, INC. will facilitate the exercise of Data Subject rights in an effective and transparent manner.
APPLICATION OF ADDITIONAL TERMS
The Additional Terms for EU and EEA Visitors and Users applies when:
The Data Subject creates or shares Personal Data via a relationship with GLOBAL COOLING, INC. and is located within the European Union (EU) or the European Economic Area (EEA);
Such relationship is within the scope of GDPR; and
GLOBAL COOLING, INC. functions as a Data Controller when processing the Personal Data for such Data Subject.
Should the above Privacy Notice or other Privacy Notices at GLOBAL COOLING, INC. conflict with the Additional Terms for EU or EEA Visitors and Users, this section will prevail as to Data Subjects in the EU or EEA.
HOW WE CONDUCT CROSS-BORDER TRANSFERS OF YOUR PERSONAL DATA
GLOBAL COOLING, INC. may transfer your Personal Data across borders to GLOBAL COOLING, INC. and our representatives, affiliates, third party partners and service providers in the United States and other countries where we do business. In the event of a cross-border transfer of your Personal Data, if the country to which we transfer your Personal Data is not a recipient of an adequacy decision from the European Commission, and if the transfer is not made under a derogation that does not require additional suitable protections, then we provide appropriate or suitable safeguards for such cross-border transfers as required by law, via the EU standard contractual clauses.
AUTOMATED DECISION MAKING
GLOBAL COOLING, INC. does not use automated decision-making, including profiling, in a way that produces legal effects concerning you or that similarly significantly affects you. We also do not use automated decision-making, including profiling, based on any special categories of Personal Data.
RETENTION OF PERSONAL DATA
GLOBAL COOLING, INC. retains your Personal Data only for as long as is reasonably necessary to accomplish the purposes for which it was collected, and as permitted by applicable law. In many cases, this will require retention through the period of the business relationship, or as needed for business administration, tax and/or legal purposes. We may retain backups and archives that may include your Personal Data as long as reasonably necessary to comply with applicable law.
SPECIAL CATEGORIES OF PERSONAL DATA
GLOBAL COOLING, INC. will not, other than in exceptional circumstances, collect and process any special categories of your Personal Data.
YOUR RIGHTS
GDPR grants rights to Data Subjects regarding the processing of Personal Data. With regards to your Personal Data, you may have the right to:
Request access to your Personal Data;
Request rectification of your Personal Data;
Request erasure of your Personal Data (e.g., update or correct your Personal Data);
Request to restrict our processing of your Personal Data;
Object to our processing of your Personal Data;
Request data portability;
Withdraw consent to the processing of your Personal Data (without affecting the lawfulness of processing based on consent before withdrawal); and/or
Lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority.
In certain circumstances, GLOBAL COOLING, INC. will need to use your Personal Data even though you may have asked us to delete or restrict or if you objected to our use of it. If this is necessary, we will do so in a lawful, fair and transparent manner. Furthermore, if you revoke consent, prior uses and disclosures will not be affected, and we may otherwise continue to process Personal Data as permitted or required by law.
CONTACT US
To exercise your rights or for any questions regarding this Privacy Notice, our privacy practices, or our processing of your Personal Data, please contact GLOBAL COOLING, INC. at info@stirlingultracold.com or at Stirling Ultracold, Division of Global Cooling, Inc., 6000 Poston Road, Athens, OH 45701 USA.
Solutions for
Clinical Trials
Laboratory
Financial Savings
Energy Savings
Research Facilities
Sustainability
Ultra-Low Freezers
Site Map
© 2020 Global Cooling Inc.
All rights reserved.
Site by Midwest New Media, LLC
© 2020 Stirling Ultracold, Global Cooling Inc. All rights reserved.
Site by Midwest New Media, LLC
This site uses cookies to provide the best possible visitor experience. By continuing to use this site, you agree that we can save them on your device. Find out more on how we use cookies and how you can change your settings.I understandPrivacy & Cookies Policy
Close
Privacy Overview
This website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these cookies, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may have an effect on your browsing experience.
Necessary
Necessary
Always Enabled
Necessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. This category only includes cookies that ensures basic functionalities and security features of the website. These cookies do not store any personal information.
Non-necessary
Non-necessary
Any cookies that may not be particularly necessary for the website to function and is used specifically to collect user personal data via analytics, ads, other embedded contents are termed as non-necessary cookies. It is mandatory to procure user consent prior to running these cookies on your website.
X
×
X
X
×
X
X
X
Warranty Registration
Warranty Registration
WHERE PURCHASEDSales Representative/Dealer/Distributor*Adachi IncorporatedBioline Global Pty LtdCanadawide ScientificCardinal HealthChester Americas, S.A. de C.V.Cole-ParmerGSE InternationalLabRepCoMarconi Equipamentos para Laboratario LtdaMIDSCIStirling UltracoldTriple RedVWR InternationalOtherABOUT YOUName*
First
Last
Title*YOUR MAILING ADDRESSJob
Function*Facility/Institution*Address*
Street Address
Address Line 2
City
State / Province / Region
ZIP / Postal Code
AfghanistanAlbaniaAlgeriaAmerican SamoaAndorraAngolaAnguillaAntarcticaAntigua and BarbudaArgentinaArmeniaArubaAustraliaAustriaAzerbaijanBahamasBahrainBangladeshBarbadosBelarusBelgiumBelizeBeninBermudaBhutanBoliviaBonaire, Sint Eustatius and SabaBosnia and HerzegovinaBotswanaBouvet IslandBrazilBritish Indian Ocean TerritoryBrunei DarussalamBulgariaBurkina FasoBurundiCambodiaCameroonCanadaCape VerdeCayman IslandsCentral African RepublicChadChileChinaChristmas IslandCocos IslandsColombiaComorosCongo, Democratic Republic of theCongo, Republic of theCook IslandsCosta RicaCroatiaCubaCuraçaoCyprusCzech RepublicCôte d'IvoireDenmarkDjiboutiDominicaDominican RepublicEcuadorEgyptEl SalvadorEquatorial GuineaEritreaEstoniaEswatini (Swaziland)EthiopiaFalkland IslandsFaroe IslandsFijiFinlandFranceFrench GuianaFrench PolynesiaFrench Southern TerritoriesGabonGambiaGeorgiaGermanyGhanaGibraltarGreeceGreenlandGrenadaGuadeloupeGuamGuatemalaGuernseyGuineaGuinea-BissauGuyanaHaitiHeard and McDonald IslandsHoly SeeHondurasHong KongHungaryIcelandIndiaIndonesiaIranIraqIrelandIsle of ManIsraelItalyJamaicaJapanJerseyJordanKazakhstanKenyaKiribatiKuwaitKyrgyzstanLao People's Democratic RepublicLatviaLebanonLesothoLiberiaLibyaLiechtensteinLithuaniaLuxembourgMacauMacedoniaMadagascarMalawiMalaysiaMaldivesMaliMaltaMarshall IslandsMartiniqueMauritaniaMauritiusMayotteMexicoMicronesiaMoldovaMonacoMongoliaMontenegroMontserratMoroccoMozambiqueMyanmarNamibiaNauruNepalNetherlandsNew CaledoniaNew ZealandNicaraguaNigerNigeriaNiueNorfolk IslandNorth KoreaNorthern Mariana IslandsNorwayOmanPakistanPalauPalestine, State ofPanamaPapua New GuineaParaguayPeruPhilippinesPitcairnPolandPortugalPuerto RicoQatarRomaniaRussiaRwandaRéunionSaint BarthélemySaint HelenaSaint Kitts and NevisSaint LuciaSaint MartinSaint Pierre and MiquelonSaint Vincent and the GrenadinesSamoaSan MarinoSao Tome and PrincipeSaudi ArabiaSenegalSerbiaSeychellesSierra LeoneSingaporeSint MaartenSlovakiaSloveniaSolomon IslandsSomaliaSouth AfricaSouth GeorgiaSouth KoreaSouth SudanSpainSri LankaSudanSurinameSvalbard and Jan Mayen IslandsSwedenSwitzerlandSyriaTaiwanTajikistanTanzaniaThailandTimor-LesteTogoTokelauTongaTrinidad and TobagoTunisiaTurkeyTurkmenistanTurks and Caicos IslandsTuvaluUS Minor Outlying IslandsUgandaUkraineUnited Arab EmiratesUnited KingdomUnited StatesUruguayUzbekistanVanuatuVenezuelaVietnamVirgin Islands, BritishVirgin Islands, U.S.Wallis and FutunaWestern SaharaYemenZambiaZimbabweÅland Islands
Country
CONTACT INFORMATIONEmail*
Phone*Contact Preference*EmailPhoneBest Time To ContactWHERE INSTALLEDFacility/Institution/Company*Building/Floor/Room Number*YOUR FREEZER APPLICATIONProduct Being StoredPreferred Setpoint TemperatureFOLLOW-UP CONTACT/NEWSLETTERStirling Ultracold reserves the right to contact you without notice of important information related to the safety and efficacy of your product.
Additionally, and only with your advance permission, Stirling Ultracold may contact you with news of new products, accessories or other offers of interest to you.YES, add me to your mailing list for your newsletter of interest to me.NO, please do not add me to your newsletter mailing list.
CLOSE
